Uh, essentially what we do with the stage in the process is, uh, an analysis,
right? I look at the,
I did like a full website crawl using hres. Um,
did like some competitive research, did a traffic projection, um,
just kinda kind of run you through everything along with my thoughts.
And then some suggested, uh, solutions.
I like to try and look for areas of opportunity during this process. Um,
you know, it's less about like, Hey, you have 10 broken links. Um, right, right.
Because that stuff doesn't move the needle. Uh, and also in all fairness,
you've done a very good job managing the websites. So, um,
there's no like glaring, glaring issues like that. It's really about, uh,
trying to stack growth on top of what you've already done. Yeah,
There's gotta be rooms to improve. 'cause we've been static in like,
we haven't made huge gains, right? Like, so I'm, yeah. To just skit your,
I need someone who knows what they're doing to look at it and say, okay,
here's where we're also not ranking for certain keywords and things. And yeah,
I need, I would like some ideas on where, how we can keep this thing growing.
Yeah, absolutely. Um, okay, so, so two simple goals, right?
For a potential working relationship. One, um,
pass over the day-to execution and strategy, uh, of ss e o. And then number two,
most importantly, generate,
generate qualified leads by increasing more hearing traffic. So,
there's two things that I'm gonna be referring to here, uh,
throughout this analysis. One is hfs, we're a big fan of hfs. Um,
and then also this is also pretty exciting.
This is the tool that we built getting ready to launch publicly on Monday,
actually. Uh, we call it traffic projection tool. Mm-hmm. Um,
essentially what it does is those three competitors that you gave me, uh,
when you signed up for this, um, it takes those keywords.
It takes your keywords, puts 'em all into a database, um,
and then spit back this table right here, right? Mm-hmm. Um,
so what this allows us to look at is all the keywords that you're ranking for in
those three competitors, rank for volume, uh,
and then current position for that keyword.
Then what we do is we go through and we assign a target position.
Meaning if we were to, you know,
run kind of our normal SS e o process based on your current performance based on
the market, um, what do we think that we could get those to, right?
In terms of the position. Um, and then from there, what it does,
it builds a growth forecast. So this is also cool 'cause it's filtered for, uh,
the Canadian SERPs. Yeah. Which addresses using kind of like,
amalgamation of all of them. So, um, as you know, right? So this is essentially,
if we were to say that your website was just gonna keep going on right now,
not making any changes, you are on kind of a break even steady path.
This number is essentially the difference between,
it's not your actual traffic number.
It's essentially if you take your starting position from this year forecasted
versus the year based on how you're doing basically a break even point.
But essentially you lose about 400 visits per month. It's not apples to apples,
but it's just more of kind of like a, a benchmark, if you will,
for what you're currently doing, right? Um, so this next scenario here,
now number two is basically saying, okay,
if we were going to make improvements on the keywords that you currently have on
the website, right? So not looking at any new keywords, um,
what do we think that we could turn that around to? Uh,
and then the final one here, the most important one is looking at, uh,
basically kind of an addressable market. It's not a total addressable market,
if you will, but it's essentially looking at the competitors, looking at gaps,
and then looking for new opportunities. Um,
and I'll show you some better charts that will show this. Uh, so again, just,
just real quick on how we filter this data,
I'm gonna go ahead and filter out anything that we've excluded.
So we exclude keywords that are, um,
we know are relevant, right?
I go through this and actually comb through this manually.
So a lot of keywords get picked up, especially,
and this is where also this analysis is important because if you just look at
hres and you look at, I think it was, uh, this one, St.
St lawyers, do they get a ton of traffic? Um,
but when a lot of it's not necessarily keywords we want is the thing with them,
like, yeah, that's exactly my point, right?
And that's why this analysis is so important because I went through and I
filtered those out. Yeah. So if you just look at those keywords, it's like, oh,
whoa, they're killing it.
But then they create a lot of like fluff content around like K P M G
layoffs,
just kind of like big co corporate company layoffs that they're probably just
attract people in. Um, that stuff is okay,
but it's really not the focus of what we like to work on because it really
doesn't generate leads, right? Um, just kind of burns resource and, and,
and picks up traffic.
So what I did though is I filter for localized keywords and then
service-based keywords, right? So anything employment based,
anything disability based, Toronto, Canada,
all those different areas that you're operating in. Um,
and what I'll just kind of run you through these percentages are a little bit
better to look at, right?
So essentially saying business as usual on a pace to lose about 8% of traffic
improvement. This is not the best one, but this is my favorite one down here,
the total addressable market. Um, so what's cool about this toes,
you can click in each one is, and I'll send you the link so you can go through,
through this on your own. Yeah. Um,
essentially just kind of plots a forecast for next year, right?
In terms of just continuing, continuing on the path that you're on.
This one is then looking at basically improving on the pages that you currently
have. And then again, the final one is, is a total,
I hate calling it total addressable market,
but just kind of like a total growth potential based on,
on the keywords provided, right? Um,
so it just kind of shows you the trajectory of what it could be.
And we can also then use this number to look at potential r o i forecasts just
to understand, you know, where you could be at. Um,
do you have any questions on that? Just very simple. Essentially the, the,
the big learning points here is that there's keywords out there for you to grow
on. Um, and as you already know, there's,
there's more opportunity in the market,
which is actually good for a site like yours because, um, you know,
one hypothesis could be that, you know,
we've kind of covered all the topics that we could. Um, but again,
our focus is not on the top, top funnel fluff content.
It's more at the bottom funnel, transactional based keywords.
And that's what I wanna focus on. Um,
so when we get into the analysis here, so a,
you're doing a lot of really good things. I give give you a lot of credit,
David, you know,
a lot more about s e o and especially when it comes to the execution of seo.
SEOs is probably the most important part here because people know about s e o,
they're like, yeah, we need to create content, but they don't. Right? Um,
you've done a very, very good job building a highly functional,
usable website with really good content. Um, that being said,
there's definitely area room for improvement and I hyper-focused on the
local side of this because I think this is where you're gonna see the most
conversion based traffic come from, right? Yep. So this report here,
um, it's cool inside of Rex, if you can see it or not. Um,
I basically just took this sub folder page here 'cause you're all the,
all these pages are structured, right?
So basically what this report is now showing is all the pages that have
location in them to see how they're performing.
So what we see here is keyword volume position.
And this is only gonna pull through keywords that are ranking too.
So there's all these keywords that you're not currently ranking for. Um, yeah.
Like ranking
S**t for all these keywords. And that's part of why scratching my head, right?
Like the only reason we rank at all is we're in the local pack.
Yeah. And I'll talk about that in a second. Yeah.
So you can see the top position that you have is position 12,
which essentially is non-existent, right?
So it's a good thing though because you're indexed, right?
So you're in what we call striking distance, not huge keywords per se,
but with some OnPage, which we'll talk about in some link building.
We can definitely punch these up to get on the top page. Um,
and this is also where again,
I see the most area of opportunity is improvement on these specific pages
from an OnPage point of view. So like, these are pretty thin, right? Yeah.
They're just going through and beefing these up and I know it could be a
resource thing, it's a pain in the ass. Also, then looking at these,
these are great pages, I love these. Um, but on deeper analysis, again,
it looks like the FAQs are the same across pages. Um,
so just going through and really hyper focusing on creating just a better
localized experience on these pages, right? Yep. Um, which is,
which is a pretty easy opportunity. Uh, so this,
this section here just refers to that, uh, only a handful of pages of ranking.
This is another kind of important, uh, I,
I know we talked about your focus on disability because it's,
it's a better quality case. There's more money in it. Yep. Um,
so when it comes to local, though, this is interesting, right? This is just a,
a national search. It's almost call it like 33% more.
It's, it's about a third percent more, right? From employment versus disability.
Um, again, knowing that disability is your bread butter,
that's what you want to focus on.
But there's things that we can do to target these keywords without taking the
focus off disability keywords. Okay? Yeah. Right? Um,
one of those would just be creating organic landing pages.
'cause all these are focused on disability, right? Which is fine,
there's no issue with that. Um,
but essentially just creating more pages under the location trees. Mm-hmm. Uh,
targeting employment-based keywords. That would be around one, right.
Two would be going through, and this is a very thin page.
Two is just providing more supporting content around employment, um,
from a bottom to mid funnel point of view. Right? Just so just
That's a whole new, like this is a blue ocean area because I haven't,
I only set that up as a placeholder because it is an area I want to grow. Yep.
Um, and those cases can be profitable if Yeah.
But I haven't done anything on them yet, as you
Can see it. Yep. And I have a, a, like a mini pitch here that's, it's,
it's a little bit outside the scope,
but I'm just gonna skip down to it real quick. And that would be to,
and I'll get back to all stuff in a second. But that would be to do, um,
that would be to do LSAs local service ads for employment to see if you'd want
to invest further into employ. Like, because it, it, it's,
the thing with s e o is we're talking about months and months and months and
resources burned on creating content and building links. And then it's like,
Ryan, I can you turn off the employment stuff because they're just, it's just,
it's not profitable for us. It's not, it's just not worth our time.
So using paid search at a very limited spend to dis to like discover these
keywords,
to kick the tires on them to see if it's an avenue that you want to go down, um,
could be, uh, an easier way to answer that question for us as opposed to,
you know, just being like, Hey, there's keyword searches for unemployment,
so we should create content around it. Right. Um, yeah, I'm
Looking for outside the box here.
I I'm looking for you to challenge 'cause I have my own way of doing things that
I've done for a decade here, and I need, I need someone to shake it up.
One thing though, may not be LSAs in Canada. I've not,
we've not had them yet in the markets that I've seen. Okay. But
Yeah, I was doing some research on that. That's a fair point.
But it, but there's still Google ads.
Yeah, a hundred percent. A hundred percent. Um, and that would be up to us,
honestly, obviously to figure that out. But just like,
just to kind of like a quick, a quick little thing there. Um, again,
before this is like kind of what we do best and what really what we pivot into
is, is kind of like holistic search marketing, right?
So what we're looking at is kind of like a vertical integration of keywords,
right?
So understanding these are all the keywords that are relevant to your business
and have conversion value. Yep. Um, two is what's the best way to rank for them?
Is it content marketing? Is it G M B? Is it advertising?
So as long as you're open to that, then we can build kind of a strategy that,
you know, is focused more on outcome as opposed to rankings,
I guess is maybe the right way to say. Um, so, uh, either way, you know,
next call I'll flush that a little bit more. So I also crawl the website,
like I said, um, just use hres, uh, pretty, pretty simple crawl.
I've used it before. Um, minor things with like redirects. And again,
usually I don't like to focus too much on like a website of your size.
You can have some technical error in Google will just be fine with it. Um,
'cause it's not like a massive thing.
Although you do have a forum on the website, which,
which I discovered through the crawl, which, um, I love, by the way.
It's the forum. Yeah.
Is That's
The beast, man. That's on.
Yeah. I couldn't even finish the crawl. Yeah.
That thing's been successful.
Yeah.
It's not, uh, it's on discourse. It's on that software, whatever,
like it's hosted by discourse. I just have it, uh,
it's not hosted in WordPress or anything like that. It's hosted on discourse.
Okay. Yeah. So, so that would be something that, uh, I would,
I'm gonna wanna bring Caesar and he's kind of our directive operations and
strategy chief. Um, I love it personally. 'cause I think it gives you,
it gives you a massive footprint in the SERPs, right? Yeah.
Also a community-based thing,
which I very smart way to integrate community into business. Yeah. And
It's a very active community too.
Very active too. Which I really like. Right? Yeah. Um,
so what I would probably want to do though is help you wrangle it in, because I,
like the site is so big now, I couldn't even get through the full crawl. Right?
So maybe
It shouldn't be on my website is what you're, is that what you're saying?
Like maybe
Well that's, that's what we'd want to engage and figure out.
'cause I don't have the answer to that. Like,
there's all sorts of hypotheticals. We could say, well, it's probably gen,
it's generating links, it's generating traffic and that's always good.
And especially if it's engaged traffic, it's good signal with Google,
but is it potentially cannibalizing pages?
Is it too heavy in terms of getting our pages discovered? Um,
you know,
or is it con like basically we'd wanna do some sort of business case analysis
where it's just,
is this contributing to growth or is this contributing to potentially
stagnation? And, um,
so we'd wanna take a deeper lead that would be kind of like the technical
analysis we'd wanna do. And I'll run it through and,
and when we get through this is looking at like the redirect.
So there's a bunch of redirect chains, which are taking place,
happens quite a bit, you know, like you change URLs, change landing pages,
but they're all around these local pages, right?
So we just wanna get that stuff cleaned up. We hurting them. Yeah. Using to do,
yeah. It's just one of the technical things I found. And then again,
like putting together a strategy,
kind of like we do it, like, we don't work with e-commerce anymore,
but we work with a lot of e-commerce shops.
It was kind of like putting together like how do we handle so much
content and product pages and like righting, decaying,
redirects outta stock in stock. Kind of similar for the form right?
Is like putting together maybe like a quarterly or twice annual review process
where we go through and we look at potentially closing threads and redirecting
threads. Yes. Cleaning up four oh fours. Um, you know, stuff along that nature,
um, where it's incredibly time consuming for you to do that.
But it's probably getting to the point where, again,
I couldn't even finish the fall. I was like,
I got a full-time member. I got a full-time content manager that we can,
she's very keen, she's a jour, she had a journalism degree. Like she's,
she's looking for direction. So any of this stuff, we can just put her on it,
man. I gotta,
Okay, perfect. That, that, that, that's helpful. Like
Link building. I've talked to her about link building, but I don't really,
we've never really got to that point yet. So like,
there's a bunch of things like press releases.
Like she's worked in journalism and she's worked at other magazines and things.
So I think like she's a great resource I wanna start using.
Yeah, no, that's, that's very helpful. Um, because after me, through this,
you know, I'll still put together a proposal,
but that helps me to understand Yeah.
Maybe we do a little bit more of a consultative approach as opposed to a done
for you approach if she's, if she's a good resource. Um,
She's great. Yeah. Like, I like
The content's great that you have. So I, I can, she looks like she's valuable.
Um, so just continue continuing on, just going through, like again, I,
my focus was on service pages, local pages,
and then I call it like chunky content. So like, more like your pillar pages,
right? Um, you already know this. We talked a little bit about this.
They could do some links. Um, this scholarship program looks good.
It's generating links that are building authority,
but definitely looking at building some direct links to more of these key pages.
Mm-hmm. Um, like again, so this is,
this is a report here of just your top pages by links, so we can see
Oh yeah, yeah.
We can see the number of over here. This is the what, the follow on.
So like we don't see any local pages in here. Um, you know, there's,
there's some images that are getting links to that we could potentially do some
redirects and stuff with, get to get cute with it. Um,
but basically just a targeted link building campaign.
And there's a number of ways that we can do that. Um,
which we'll talk about if we talk more about the scope. Like there's pr there's,
we'll, we'll, we'll get to in a second. Um,
Yeah.
And then, sorry, do you have a question?
No, no. I was gonna say that's, and again,
I got the in-house resource dedicated. She could really,
because I know link building's the toughest thing to do really in terms of Yeah.
Follow up needed and you gotta be stay on it. And, um,
Yep. So, uh, this was the other thing. This is kind of the final part too.
So you're, you're right,
I actually have some software that shows us maps pack tracking.
And while you're not ranking good organically for the local pages,
your maps packs are, are actually really good for anything disability based.
And I only check three year locations. I checked Toronto,
I think maybe Nova Scotia,
but we'd wanna set up some sort of tracking for that too. Yeah,
We're on, we're on, I think we're on top of the all except for the Ottawa one.
Okay. Yeah. So just got
Ranked. Like I just got enough reviews to get us ranked there.
Okay, perfect. Um,
so what we would wanna do there too is while we get into this, I'll just, well,
I'll just get into the solutions, right, because I'll just Yep. Repeat myself.
Okay. So the first thing is a website quality audit.
This is a proprietary audit that we built in-house that would cover like all the
technical stuff, the redirects, the forum strategy. Yes. Um,
and kind of like a general like website architecture strategy, right?
In terms of like scaling maybe to the next level in terms of content.
Where do we store this content? How does it interrelate, um, et cetera.
So that would be one solution. Two would be content marketing.
So it wouldn't be done for you content marketing.
It would be kind of like a content,
it would be kind of like the website quality app, but specifically for content,
right? Yep. Assets have what needs updating and then again Perfect.
To work with. Um, what's, what's the, uh, the content person's name?
What was her name?
Uh, her name is, um, Maddie.
Maddie. Okay. So working with Maddie to, um,
basically fill up like a content matrix, content calendar, all that stuff.
And we would handle kind of like the heavy legwork in terms of the research.
Yeah. And that can be done on a monthly basis, quarterly basis. Yeah. Um,
and then, you know, work through her to get that stuff done. Yeah. Okay.
So let's talk about links. So yes,
there's a couple of things that we can do with links. So, um,
I always recommend, and like we make no money off this, but if they're like,
PR is the best formula building like true PR building. Mm-hmm. I agree. Yeah,
it's expensive. Um, and it's not always reliable.
'cause PR companies are like, they're such an anomaly in the agency space.
It's like the one service where they charge like 10,
15 grand a month potentially with like,
that's not tied to any real business results or like coverage guarantees or
anything. Um,
so like we can work with you and Naty to put together kind of like a really
good spec sheet to potentially go out and do like a PR sprint maybe. Uh,
you've got a lot of good content, you're good on video.
There's a whole bunch of things that we could do with that, right?
Yeah.
There's even some original research and things we could do that would be of
interest to media. Like there's a bunch of things we could do.
Yep. That, so that would be like option one that would be the most expensive,
but probably also the best results, right? Um,
option two is we often work with, uh, she's a contractor.
She's really, really good with, she's becoming more of like kind of an,
i I call her like an, like a an S E O P R person. Right. She's really,
really good at, are you familiar with helper reporter out Harrow Link building?
H a r o? Um, it's kind of like, so Bench,
it's kind of like Cision, but they,
so essentially you sign up for these lists and they send you on a daily basis
three times a day, all these different requests from journalists,
bloggers who are looking basis for Okay.
Yeah. I've heard of couple reporter out. Yeah, I've heard
Of that. Yep. So we could manage that for you.
And we basically just charge per placement, I think it's like six or 700,
a hundred bucks per placement. Um,
and when you co when you compare and contrast that to PR where it's like 10
grand a month, they're usually getting between like three and eight place. Yeah.
I'm not gonna be able to
Do 10 grand a month, so
I wouldn't, I wouldn't recommend any out there because I like to present,
you know? Yeah. I the options Right. And lead up to you. Um,
so we can do that for you. And that's basically like a batch of links,
like 20 or 30 of them.
And she's really good with that too because she actually just, so I use her for,
I, I, I, I use her for myself. That's how I found her. Um,
and she just got me on like a local news video, which was great.
They interviewed me for five minutes on like AI and the status of marketing,
all that stuff. Um, so like she's be,
she's getting better and better and better with that stuff too.
So that's like paper placement.
And then the final piece of it that you would use us to do would just be like,
what I call like SEO O link building.
So like we've got a database and bloggers that we've worked with the last 15
years, and those are much lower costs. Those are like three 50 to 400 per link.
Um, and that can be, you know, purely based on, on your budget.
And we can get very surgical with those placements too. Yeah. Right.
So that would be the,
and then the final option would be a consulting with Maddie to
figure out what are the options that she could do for like, her own outreach.
That would probably be the cheapest option for you. Right. Um,
but in terms of results, you know, it can be, it can be a mixed bag, right?
Yeah. Um,
so we'll talk about kind of like how we can potentially put something together
that, that works on all levels, um, for links. Uh,
and then locally focused ss e o. So again, this is like really improving those,
the content on those pages, um, putting together like a review,
kind of like ongoing review strategy for you. Um, updating,
there's a whole bunch of stuff that we do from a local point of view.
It's becoming like actually a focal point of what we do for attorneys.
'cause it's just
So important. Yeah.
So important. Um, yeah, go ahead. No,
I said, I said I agree. Yeah. Okay. I do have a review. Like, we're,
we're getting reviews like every month we're getting a few, like we,
they're kind of spread out between the different offices, but I,
I basically do a, I do a debrief with every client myself,
even if I didn't handle a case and I basically have a funnel to get them to
leave us a review at the end of the case is one of the things that we're,
that's where most of our reviews come from.
And then I get the sales team to kind of get them for people who maybe didn't be
a client, but were happy with our help. Yeah. But yeah,
the reviews is huge. Yeah. The LSAs, I wish we had them.
I don't think we got them, but we, you can figure that out. Yeah.
So, so, so then I, so like, again, this is kind of like,
was kind of like my pitch. Like I said, it doesn't, we don't have to do this.
Um, you know, like your site performs very well organically. So like,
I have no doubt that if we create the right content and build some links to some
stuff around employment law that you'll rank for it.
This would be kind of like an exploratory approach if you wanted to be,
you know, once we start talking about now,
like stacking channels too and stacking systems,
it becomes much more of a lead generation approach,
if that's be the right way to put it. Right. Where we're,
we're tracking things pretty meticulously. Um,
we're looking at keywords much differently. Right. Um,
so optional. Completely optional. I'll throw it in a quote. Um,
'cause it would be an additional cost, but just for context, right.
And I'll scope this out in a proposal after this,
assuming everything looks good, but all this together, and this would be,
this would range anywhere from like 4,500 a month to six to $7,000 a month
depending on which type of link building you wanted to go with. Right?
That would be like the biggest discretionary in cost. Um,
everything else in here would be for essentially everything that we just talked
about. Um, like ongoing monthly,
kind of like content maintenance and working with Maddie Consulting,
all that stuff that would be baked into that cost. The,
the ads would be a separate cost that I can,
that I can scope up for you separately. Yeah. Um, and also too,
like this doesn't have to be done right away. You know,
like this can be done anytime in the future after we,
maybe we wanna do three months of like getting the ss e o on track,
seeing how that,
I did wanna like, yeah, like I'm, I really trust you on the ss e o stuff.
So it's like I really wanna make sure like get it audited, get it,
get it on the right track, uh, and then look at, okay, how do we kind of,
'cause that is like, that is the big differentiator. Like we,
I believe we do have the best content. It's how do we keep,
that's why I like keeping the content in-house.
'cause I find you can keep your quality level up. Um, but yeah,
no, this sounds all good to me, Ryan, for sure. Okay.
Okay.
I think I would start with like,
I would like to start with seeing if we can get Maddie doing the link.
Like give her,
give her a chance to do it and see if she's able to execute on it. Sure. Um,
because she does have media. Like she, she is,
she does have connections and things and she is a journalist, so it does,
she's got a different level of, of, uh,
competence there in doing the PR and stuff.
But I'd like to try to get her doing that rather than just grinding
out more content. I kind of told her I don't wanna grind out content.
I want to improve content and build links. Really.
Yep. That's fair. Okay. So, so assuming you're all good with this, um, well,
do you have any questions on this? Anything? Anything that's in here? No,
This is exactly what I was looking for. Okay. I was,
I was hoping you weren't gonna tell me that the,
the whole architecture has gotta be like, done over because it sucks.
No, you're, you're doing too well for that, right? I mean, yeah.
I got a very thin, like, it's a very basic, uh, the, uh,
the theme is very basic too, so it's fast. Right.
I like it, man. Honestly, like, I think that
like a lot of people will come in here and be like, oh,
you need a new website design. Like, I don't,
I actually think that like the simpler and more focused on Yeah. It's like,
you know who your audience is to like, these people aren't here to look at,
look at like flashing images like they need. I know. Yeah. You know,
and they want to talk to somebody and they want to access them. Yeah.
As fast as possible. That's all that matters, you know? Yeah, yeah. Um, so I,
I really like it. I think, you know, there's some, again,
like six months a year from now, like there's things we can do with like,
maybe like your webinar pages and integrating video content and stuff like that.
Yeah. Um, 'cause I did go on your YouTube channel.
I really like all the stuff that you have and that opens up like a whole new
avenue.
Well yeah. And I've kind of fell off the wagon on that. Like,
I need to get back to doing YouTube again.
And, and that would be something that we can potentially help out with too.
Like I, again,
the way I look at content is like one central backbone and then it's just like,
okay, what's just like I said with keywords, right?
It's the same thing with content. Like what's the best medium, the best way to,
to, to get this message across to this content. Um,
and especially for lawyers,
like your ability to create video just sets you apart right away. It
Does, yeah. Video
Is right away. So, um, we
Get a lot of leads off the video.
Like a lot of people use the video too to like reassure themselves that they're,
you're gonna be a good guy to deal with type of thing.
So it's kind of used both ways, like it's lead generation,
but it's also reassurance. I find
A hundred percent. I I, you don't have to tell me. Yeah,
Yeah. You know, you know. Well that's why I'm talking to you. I got your book,
I've seen your videos. I'm like, 'cause it's,
this is a space where I'm, I'm very,
I'm very protective about the website and things like that. Uh,
so I'm glad we don't have to rejigger the whole thing and there's,
looks like there's just some tech,
I know there will be some technical issues with it.
So Yeah, the, the way I see this is really more of like,
you've already got the momentum going.
You just don't have the time to keep managing it. Right.
And we can step in at a price that makes sense. Um, yeah.
And I've got a content manager who's not an s e o expert and I don't like,
I don't want her to be right.
Like I want her to be able to take directions and like,
she's great 'cause she fills a lot of roles. She hosts the webinars.
I do do like, she handles our email newsletter.
Like our email newsletter is just like every Wednesday.
That thing is like clockworks and she's been doing it
Actually. Yeah.
Yeah. It's great. Yeah. You gotta have a,
gotta have a full-time person on this or it just falls off
A hundred percent. Yeah. Um, okay, perfect. So in terms of next steps here,
what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna take this and put together a scope of work with
the exact pricing, timelines, everything that you need to make a decision,
um, potentially partner up with us.
Awesome man. And you're done in Florida, aren't you? Yeah,
I'm I in Florida.
Yeah. Okay. Right on. Good enough. Yeah, I'm heading down there later, but it's,
me and my wife are going to a conference, but it's up in Orlando so far away.
Far away from where you're at. But yeah. Love Florida.
Yeah. It's all fire right now. Every everyone, everyone is moving.
I would move there in a heartbeat if my wife would go,
but she's French and likes sit up here too much. But I would go in a second man.
Florida is definitely my jam.
Florida was, it's so crazy. I've been here for about 10 years now. Yeah.
And when I moved here it was like kind of the butt of the jokes in America a
lot. It was.
Yeah. Florida, not
Anymore. Not anymore, man. Everyone wants to come here now. No state income tax.
It's like the politics here is very different than on the west coast too. Yeah,
exactly. Yeah. It's become
The politics. That's my politics. Like the whole, the whole kind of, uh,
idea of Florida is like right where I want to go
To go. I've really grown into it as I've gotten older and um, yeah,
Florida's my home now. I'm, I'm bossed through and through. Um, yeah.
But like Florida is, is, I can't imagine living anywhere else now.
No, I hear you. Well, Ryan, look,
I look forward to working with you and I'm hoping I can be a success story for
you.
Yeah, absolutely. I mean, you already are, you know, it's,
working with clients like you is is kind of our dream because uh,
we don't have to spend too much time on stuff that doesn't move the needle.
Right. You got, you don't
Have to sell me on the idea of that content will work for sure. I know it works.
I just know I've meet,
I've hit my level of where I can go and I need like help to keep this thing
going to the next level. And also knowing like where we're going in the future.
'cause I don't think Google is gonna allow someone like me to live off of
organic search indefinitely.
It's definitely moving towards you gotta be in the paid. Yeah.
And I can get you guys, I, we did a lot of paid ads and things,
so I have a lot of data on that. Um, but I,
I'll def I'm definitely looking to get back into paid ads here as part of this
whole thing as well at some point. So
Yeah, I mean we, uh, once you're with us, man, we can take care of if,
if we can't take care of it,
then I have the biggest network that you can imagine of anything that you could
potentially need from designers, developers, everything. So. Alright David,
it was great talking.
Have a good weekend. Take.